[
    {
        "front": "ひとつ",
        "back": "一つ \nOne (thing)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "いちがつ",
        "back": "一月 \nJanuary",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ついたち",
        "back": "一日 \nThe 1st day of a month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふたつ",
        "back": "二つ \nTwo (things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "にがつ",
        "back": "二月 \nFebruary",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふつか",
        "back": "二日 \nThe 2nd day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ふたり",
        "back": "二人 \nTwo People",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "みっつ",
        "back": "三つ \nThree (Things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "さんがつ",
        "back": "三月 \nMarch",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "みっか",
        "back": "三日 \nThe 3rd day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "よん",
        "back": "四 \nFour",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "よっつ",
        "back": "四つ \nFour (things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しがつ",
        "back": "四月 \nApril",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "よっか",
        "back": "四日 \nThe 4th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつつ",
        "back": "五つ \nFive(things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ごがつ",
        "back": "五月 \nMay",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "いつか",
        "back": "五日 \nThe 5th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "むっつ",
        "back": "六つ \nSix (things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ろくがつ",
        "back": "六月 \nJune",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "むいか",
        "back": "六日 \nThe 6th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "なな",
        "back": "七 \nSeven",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ななつ",
        "back": "七つ \nSeven (things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "しちがつ",
        "back": "七月 \nJuly",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "なのか",
        "back": "七日 \nThe 7th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "やっつ",
        "back": "八つ \nEight",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "はんがつ",
        "back": "八月 \nAugust",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ようか",
        "back": "八日 \nThe 8th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ここのつ",
        "back": "九つ \nNine (things)",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "くがつ",
        "back": "九月 \nSeptember",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "ここのか",
        "back": "九日 \nThe 9th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "とお/じゅう",
        "back": "十 \nTen",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうがつ",
        "back": "十月 \nOctober",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "とおか",
        "back": "十日 \nThe 10th day of month",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    },
    {
        "front": "じゅうぶんな",
        "back": "十分な \nEnough",
        "chapter": "N5 K2"
    }
]